(Scene:)Sheldon...
(Amy:)it's okay with me that
you're not perfect.
(Sheldon:)Can I have one more moment
with Leonard?
(Howard:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)Amy just hurt my feelings.
I want to break up with her.
(Howard:)Now, I never thought
I'd say this, but I'm
(Howard:)kind of excited to see Sheldon.
(Howard:)I never thought I'd say this,
but Penny got a job today.
(Howard:)She did?
(Bernadette:)Well, the only reason she got it
(Bernadette:)is 'cause the guy
who interviewed her loves me.
(knocking)
(clears throat)
(Howard(answering a knock on the door):)What do you want?
(Stuart:)I, uh, kind of got the feeling
(Stuart:)you might not be okay with me
staying at your mom's.
(Howard:)You're right, I'm not.